Uladzimir Yeudakimovich

Software Engineer (JavaScript)

Contacts

• Phone: +48 884 603 351

Skype: live:be52441aa4a87669

Email: uladzimir.yeudakimovich@gmail.com

• Github: https://github.com/uladzimir-yeudakimovich

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/uladzimir-yeudakimovich/

General information

I have 3 years' experience in Frontend development using JavaScript and Angular. I have thorough understanding of whole app development process, from requirements review to submission to production. I tend to apply the latest development standards into development process. I make it my goal to create a useable and intuitive user interface experience. My technology stack covers JavaScript, Angular, AngularJS, React, HTML, CSS, Sass, Less, NodeJS, ExpressJS, AWS, Serverless, MongoDB, jQuery, Responsive UI, Git and Photoshop. I am citizen of Republic of Belarus and I have polish national visa D Poland Business Harbour until 11.04.2022.

Employment History

Lifetech

02.2019 - present

OCSICO

08.2018 - 02.2019

Freelance 09.2017 – 08.2018

Middle Frontend Developer

Junior Frontend Developer

Junior Frontend Developer

Projects

FEB 2019 - PRESENT

PMS

Frontend Developer

Admin panel to set goals for employees and assess employees.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features

Tools and Technologies:

Angular10, NGRX, HTML, SASS

Lifetransfer

Web part of quick sharing files.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features

Tools and Technologies:

Angular8, HTML, SASS

Fizy

Web part development of music service.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Bug fixing
- Redesign components

Tools and Technologies:

Angular JS, Angular 7, HTML, SASS

Lifebox

Web part development of cloud service.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Bug fixing
- Style templates system

Tools and Technologies:

Angular JS, Angular7, React HTML, SASS, NodeJS, Express, Webpack

Billo

Web part development of cloud service.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Style templates system

Tools and Technologies:

Angular JS, Angular7, React HTML, SASS, NodeJS, Express, Webpack

AUG 2018 - FEB 2019 Frontend Developer

iKassa

Sales management web application.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Style templates system

Tools and Technologies:

Angular7, HTML, SASS, NodeJS, Express

Plugin

Plugin for web application.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Style templates system

Tools and Technologies:

Angular7, HTML, SASS, NodeJS, Express

Adapsys

Hotel web application.

Main responsibilities:

- Frontend development
- Including new features
- Style templates system
- Bug fixing

Tools and Technologies:

Angular4, HTML, SASS

Education

- The Rolling Scopes School: front-end development 2017-2018
- Udemy, Angular 7 course, 2018-2019
- The Rolling Scopes School: NodeJS development 2020 (https://app.rs.school/certificate/u08bjctf)
- Fullstack course in The University of Helsinki, 2020 (online)
- Node.js in Cloud AWS, 2020 (https://app.rs.school/certificate/vnl50gj7)

Languages

Belarusian: native speaker

• English: B1 level (intermediate)

• Polish: A2 level (pre-intermediate)

• Russian: native speaker